Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
No animals were hurt during
the filming of this series.
Episode 92
Come on, my lions!
We will reap the rewards of our efforts
in conquest.
Come on, my lions! Work!
Wow, Blacksmith! Wow!
Alps! Protect the catapults!
Hide the swords!
Burn! Burn everything!
Everything!
Sir Blacksmith.
Blacksmith Davut Bey!
Did you make all this preparation for me?
I am honored.
These catapults, these swords...
Look, I've burned them all!
What will you do now?
You've burned them all, Nikola.
You did.
Do you know the Phoenix?
Its name is Turk.
We resurrect if we get burned with
the belief in Islam in our hearts.
Burn it, Nikola.
Burn it.
Your fire in the afterlife will be plenty.
I don't like stories, Blacksmith Bey.
But you Turks love a story very much.
And you talk too much.
Damn it! Inhisar is gone!
Bilecik is gone!
Yarhisar and Inegöl will also be gone,
Lord Basilius.
I don't think so, Commander.
What can stop the Turks?
Their siege will never succeed.
Because they will lose everything they
have.
And they will fail!
They are up to something, my Bey.
They are going to make a move.
You mean, he seemed pretty confident,
right?
How would they know?
-Cerkutay.
-Yes, my Bey?
Beat Aktemur a little.
Then take him to his tent.
As you order, my Bey.
Come on.
Praise be! Our valiants arrived!
Master Davut!
Master Davut! Are you all right?
I am fine, my Bey. You go after that dog!
-I can't leave you alone, Master Davut!
-I am here brother, come on!
These wounds are nothing to me.
Go after that dog, my Bey!
-Come on brother!
-All right!
Come on, valiants, come with me!
Samil!
We are going after my Bey!
Nikola!
My Bey!
Bring him to me after I go.
-As you order, my Bey.
-As you order.
My Bey hunted one of the biggest
preys.
If we have Nikola, the fall of Inegol
must be soon.
Lord Nikola! His cruelness was mentioned
everywhere.
Fly in the ointment.
The suffering Nikola caused us is not
little at all.
Duty awaits. Come on!
How much time and effort have
we put into these!
All of it got wasted.
All of it!
We can replace what got burned but...
...if I don't see that dog Nikola
burn like this...
...I won't get relief.
I agree, brother. I agree.
Nikola?
Did he run away, Osman Bey?
He is our prisoner.
Alps are with him. He is coming
to the tribe with us.
Why are we taking him with us, Osman Bey?
Why didn't you slit his throat?
We should destroy that dog!
I need him alive.
I will let him go when we take Inegöl
Castle.
Are we going to bargain for the conquest?
After all he has done to our brothers it
doesn't suit us to release him.
Osman Bey.
Do we go after a feud, Turgut Bey?
We go after justice.
Could anything be better than taking
Inegol Castle by sparing a dog's life?
Tell me.
You are right. Inegöl first.
Inegöl first.
What if they don't accept the exchange,
my Bey?
Then, we will use Turgut Bey's way.
Are we powerful enough to use that way,
Osman Bey?
Everything is ruined.
We have many martyrs.
They have worked very hard until
this day.
They were forging swords day and night
for the conquest.
May all of them rest in peace.
Amen.
But...
...we won't waste their efforts.
We won't stop because we got burned.
We will attack with everything we have,
Brother.
With everything we have!
Nephew, you will go to Inegol.
As if you were a commander who was
taken prisoner, you will tell them...
...that I want the Inegöl Castle...
...in return for Nikola.
As you order, my Bey.
Bury our martyrs.
Where is Master Davut?
He is further.
Alps are checking his wound, my Bey.
Come on.
My brave grandma.
She used to tell us about my grandma
Halime and grandfather Ertugrul Gazı.
Their love was so great.
Is that so? Did they love each other
that much?
So much.
Selcen Mother used to always tell us about
them before our bedtime.
I am very curious. I wish I could
hear it as well.
My grandfather Ertuğrul faced opposition
of everyone for my grandmother Halime.
He saved her from the infidels and brought
her to his tribe.
Didn't he fear anyone?
Would a Kayı valiant ever?
My grandfather Ertuğrul was very brave
even when he was young.
He was not defeated by the enemy,
neither inside nor outside.
My grandmother fell in love with him.
My grandfather Ertuğrul went out for
gazelle hunting, but he went...
...and fell in love with my grandmother.
My grandmother Halime stayed with him
until she died.
What an epic love.
You should have heard their love
from my grandmother Selcen.
She would tell it so differently.
My brave grandmother.
My valiants!
Osman Bey is back in the tribe.
He even prisoned that dog Nikola!
Who could ever stand against my father?
Nikola's payment will be severe.
Come on, then! Let's go to the tribe!
Come on.
Master Davut is wounded!
Take him to the healing tent with alps,
Kumral Abdal.
You will die, Nikola! You deserved this!
You will die in pain!
Don't let him live even one more moment!
Inegöl Castle
Stop! Who are you?
There are things I have to tell about
Lord Nikola.
What will you say?
Who sent you?
I am one of the commanders who was
taken prisoner in Bilecik.
Osman took Lord Nikola prisoner as well.
He sent me for the bargain.
I need to speak to a senior commander.
How could this happen?
Come with me.
What happened to Nikola?
Could he ruin the headquarters?
Are you the top commander?
Who is asking?
Here is the greatest commander!
Not only the Inegöl's but also the Rome's
greatest commander!
I don't like compliments, Arius.
The only thing that encourages me is
the painful screams of the people I kill.
Who are you?
I am Alexander, one of the commanders that
Osman took prisoner.
Alexander.
When did Great Rome's commanders start
to get prisoned...
...instead of dying!
You are talented, young commander.
I am glad you didn't die.
Tell me.
Nikola destroyed the headquarters.
But Osman caught him.
They have him. He is wounded.
Osman wants to bargain with you.
Thus, he sent me.
Why did Osman send you?
Why did he trust you?
You were free.
You could've run away in peace.
Would a Turk ever trust us, Sir?
Osman didn't trust me.
He compelled me.
He was going to kill my soldiers
if I didn't come.
What a loyal commander is Alexander!
Are you loyal to your soldiers as well,
Romanos?
Commanders are not loyal to their soldiers
soldiers are loyal to commanders.
Because the leaders win the war, not
the soldiers.
What does Osman want in return for
Nikola?
Aya Nikola for the Inegöl Castle.
If you deliver the castle he will free my
soldiers and Nikola.
First Bilecik, now Inegöl...
...you talk no good, Alexander.
I believe I have to cut it!
There's no point in feeling the anger
of defeat, Romanos.
Nikola isn't gone in vain.
Our aim was to destroy the headquarters
and he managed it.
Do you think this will stop Osman?
He won't be satisfied with it. He will
build that headquarters again.
He maybe would if I wasn't going to take
over his mines tomorrow.
But, Osman won't be able to do anything
without his mines.
What about Nikola? Will we leave him
to Osman?
I can't let that happen.
We will think about this offer
for a while.
You can be our guest in the castle.
I am grateful, Sir.
I hope you can find a way to save
my soldiers and Aya Nikola.
We won't think about this offer.
Inegöl will never be Osman's!
No soldier is more precious than Rome's
lands!
I won't leave my best student to Osman!
I've already made my plan.
Trust your master.
You aren't my master.
I'm not your student.
I grow up drinking blood!
I walked through fire!
Now, whatever you do,
be quick!
Or, I'll go to Constantinople, build
an army and attack the Turks!
Your anger and army aren't
needed, Romanos.
Because, Barkın will save Nikola.
Take him too!
But he won't die so easily.
My children!
Come!
My lions!
We have martyrs.
But we don't have mourning!
That vile Nikola raided our camp
where we were preparing the conquest.
Our alps have fallen martyrs.
A valiant's bones turn to dust
but he gets remembered.
We'll remember them with
their heroism...
their efforts and their bravery!
We'll remember their part on the
path to the conquest.
They opened the path to the conquest.
We have Nikola. Either they give
the castle and take Nikola...
or we'll behead Nikola and
conquer the castle.
It's their decision.
And it's our jihad!
Allahu Akbar!
-How is Koses?
-He's in the tent. Waiting for you.
It'll be fine, Davud.
Your wound will heal.
The catapults burned.
They brought the weasel who
inflicted the wound, Master Davud.
My friend Davud!
Are you still alive?
You still breathe because my bey
ordered so, Nikola. Don't test me.
Kumral Abdal, Osman Bey wants him
alive for now.
Death and life are from Allah.
My job is causing healing.
He is wounded. But if he can speak,
his hands won't stay idle.
We should chain him.
Don't be afraid if Nikola draws
his weapon but be afraid if he speaks.
This is what this dog deserves.
Since you still can't kill me...
you all need me.
It's the end of your reign, Nikola.
Shut up!
Osman's loyal dogs!
Gencebey! Gag him!
May Allah bless your hands.
Alright. Alright.
As you say.
I'll stay out of this war.
But I want to help you secretly.
Thank you, Koses.
Thank you.
But we won't act careless
like that.
I know, you always supported me.
You risked your life.
But if you get involved with
the conquest of İnegöl...
then, the emperor will have
capitulations on you.
He will. But I'm not afraid of that.
I know, Koses.
Of course, I do.
But stay back for now.
Be ready.
We'll fight a lot. We'll fight
shoulder to shoulder.
But act like an enemy for now.
Alright. What do you want me to do?
Tell me.
Should I build an army?
Yes. But the emperor...
will think that you are building
it against me.
But you'll build an army to
fight alongside me.
Very well.
Let's say it didn't happen as you say.
They didn't give the castle.
Your catapults and weapons
are damaged. What will you do?
Since my grandfather Süleyman Shah and
my father Ertuğrul Ghazi...
we were careful with two things...
weapons and measures.
We don't put all the fruits in the same
basket. The big one is still in the bag.
Good. I see it now.
Tomorrow, İnegöl's walls will
get hit hard.
If they don't give it in peace...
that will happen.
Tell me...
what's happening?
I don't know, Osman Bey.
But for some reason...
I don't feel like returning to
that gloomy castle.
I don't know. Maybe I'm not as
nimble as I used to be.
I don't know. Maybe my
soul is tired.
All these treacheries, my losses...
I saw that light only once again.
When I got wounded,
when Edebali prayed over my head...
I didn't understand what he said...
but it felt like a sparkle in my soul.
I saw that light once again
for a short while.
Koses. That's Allah's grace...
and mercy.
We burn with that fire when
we go to jihad.
If you felt this from the prayer
over your head...
just think about what you'll feel
when you pray to your creator.
You are on the right path. Inshallah,
Allah will put us on the same line...
not only on the battlefield
but also on the salaat.
Thank you.
May I enter, Ayşe Hatun?
-Aktimur!
-Mother!
Aktimur!
My son! My son!
My Allah, thank you!
You brought me my son!
Many gratitude!
Happiness is soon, mother.
But we need a little bit more patience.
Don't I know it, son? I've been
grinning and bearing it.
I know it.
What can we do?
We'll bear a little longer.
Oh, my son.
You are standing.
Come, let's sit.
Come. You traveled.
I'll prepare you a meal. You must be
thirsty. Let me give you sherbet.
Mother, I'll leave. I must be in
the captive tent.
But you just came. You just came.
Come, sit.
-Let's sit.
-Mother.
Aktimur. Let's sit.
Alright. Alright.
You have my prayers, son.
May Allah guide you.
Be victorious with Osman Bey.
Return to your tribe and mother.
Mother!
Mashallah.
You grew up!
Kızılbeyoğlu Tribe
Thank Allah, Osman Bey is saved. And
you didn't make the mistake of taking Söğüt.
Thank Allah. Thank Allah.
But...
you know why I did it.
-I only want the best for our tribe.
-I know it.
I know, but, I couldn't
sleep since we talked.
I was feeling nervous.
Osman Bey and his tribe stood
with us during our difficult times.
Are preparations complete?
You didn't tell anyone anything, right?
As you said, my bey.
No one else knows the road.
I'll be their guide.
When you reach the upland, I'll get
the rest of the people.
Inshallah, my bey. I should be
busy with the preperations.
-May I enter, my bey?
-Come in, Hüsamettin.
The men are ready and waiting
for order, my bey.
You'll be among the ones going
to the upland.
-Don't fight back. I don't want blood.
-As you order, my bey.
-Hüsamettin.
-My bey.
If Selvi gets hurt in
any way.
I'll kill you all.
Both grief and happiness
are for humans.
Everything comes from our creator.
We had losses,
funerals...
We had martyrs...
but thank Allah that...
they all died on the right path.
Selcan Hatun put effort to gain
Allah's aproval...
until her last breath.
May Allah treat her with mercy.
-Amin.
Selcan Hatun and all our guests...
they'll be neighbors of our prophet.
Amin, my sheik.
Amin.
Our tribe grew with suffering.
As we fight the heathens with
a weapon on one hand...
we buried our martyrs with
the other hand.
It will always be like this.
We know well that...
the only thing they want...
it to continue the cause
they died for.
I swear on our martyrs that...
with Allah's approval we'll continue
this cause forever.
Amin.
-May I enter, my bey?
-Come in, Aygül.
My bey, our scouts returned.
I wanted to inform you.
The group that'll get Holafira
is on the way.
Good.
Keep the cautions high.
Holofira is under our protection.
She should be safe.
-Alps keep their eyes on her, my bey.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Aygül.
We waited for you at iftar but
we know how you feel.
-We didn't want to disturb you.
-I know.
Thank you, Bala.
But the pain is so new.
I'll look for her at the iftar...
Of course, you'll feel the
pain, my daughter.
separation burns your heart.
I know it.
But this separation isn't forever.
The eternal home is waiting
for us.
Our prophet lived for 63 years
in this world.
So, we shouldn't be sad about death.
We should always remember the dead.
And keep their place fresh with
prayers and Qur-an.
When you reunite in the afterlife...
it'll feel like you were never
separated.
Come on, sit with us.
We need extra caution
on the way back.
Rest well now. After getting Holofira,
no one will blink.
Don't worry, Alexander. We'll
get Holofira to her aunt safely.
As you ordered, their uniforms
aren't damaged, sir.
Very well done.
I don't want any mistakes.
You'll go to Kayı Tribe.
-And you'll get Holofira.
-Be at ease, sir.
-We remember every word.
-Good.
You are finally awakened.
You are alive for now.
You'll regret not killing me, Osman Bey.
Everything has a time.
You are a very smart man.
You'll use me as a card. But
it's in vain.
No one will give you anything
for me.
Especially İnegöl.
Do you think that you can get
İnegöl in return for me?
Now is not the time to ask questions
but to answer them.
Say it. Who are you working with?
You are asking Master Darius.
You'll see who he is, only
when you feel...
his sword upon your neck.
By the way, Davud...
Davud the Smith, yes.
I wounded him badly. He made a lot of
noise. He must be dead already.
Master Davud is alive.
He'll be better.
-But you--
-Let him be alive, Osman Bey.
Let him live. I took so much
from you.
I took your alps.
I took your women, children...
I took your loved ones.
I took your beloved brother Savcı.
I won't leave a single person
around you. I'll take them all!
What can you do to me?
You can kill me at most.
Go on and take it.
Take my life.
Is that so?
You can't take anything from me.
Those who fall for the
right path...
get rewarded with heaven.
You can't take anything from me.
The one who has the will of steel,
doesn't get affected by anything.
Your intention is to play with my
anger and get yourself killed.
You want to kill yourself to
save İnegöl.
Your bravery won't work on me...
and I won't lose to my anger.
Either you live or die...
I'll take İnegöl.
Either I live or die, I won't give
you İnegöl!
Oh, my beautiful mother.
She was a mother to us all.
All of this tribe.
She loved you a lot, Olofira.
I loved her too.
You too. I love all of you.
You are so different.
What's different about us?
Come, tell me.
Everything.
Where you live, where
you sleep.
Then, the river, the tents...
no children can feel like they
are in a cage.
My pretty girl.
You won't feel like you
are in a cage again.
If that cage is a dungeon for you,
then you won't go there.
Come on, Alahaddin.
Don't think that much.
You rush for everything, brother.
Be patient.
-To make the right move, I must think.
-No.
For the right move, you need
to act fast.
Without wasting time,
you'll grab the enemy's throat!
That's through for battle, brother.
But rushing in this game...
makes you lose it.
I'll beat you and show you
what makes you lose it.
Alahaddin, do they play
this game...
in İznik, Bursa,
Constantinople?
I don't know. Holofira knows though.
-Her aunt lives there.
-Right. Holofira knows it.
I wonder how is it like there.
Constantinople.
Brother, one day, I'll go there.
Attacking from here isn't reasonable.
We've been hearing it.
Nikola strengthened his walls.
You are right, Gündüz Bey. But that's
the shortest way to the inner castle.
If we enter from a single front, we'll
get stuck. We'll have high casualties.
Gündüz Bey. Turgut Bey is right.
We shouldn't have high casualties.
If needed...
we can hit the walls for weeks.
But we don't know what to expect inside.
I said it's not reasonable, Konur.
I didn't say it's impossible.
Let's wait for Osman Bey and
see what he says.
Behold! Osman Bey!
-Salam Alaikum.
-Alaikum Salam.
We were tasked with the campaign,
not the victory.
But many gratitudes to my mighty
Allah that...
we were destined for victory.
Bilecik Castle is ours.
Now, İnegöl Castle is
our target.
We have Nikola now.
And he values the castle
over his life.
He'll do anything to stop
the exchange.
We'll siege the castle.
We can siege the castle, my bey.
We'll cut the lines of supply too.
But we have no catapults to hit the walls
or battering rams to break the gate.
My bey, this will be a long siege.
Also, we'll suffer the reinforcements
of the emperor and the other lords.
We can cut the support lines.
But if they come for a battle,
we'll be in the open no matter what.
It'll be as you said.
We'll cut the supply lines.
We'll put scouts on all sides
of the castle.
And not a single reinforcement will
reach İnegöl.
We'll do all this in a very
short time.
It'll be over in a day.
The place where they burned...
was where the weapons
were being built.
But not where they are kept.
We hid the ammunition with
Cerkutay's trade...
and took them to every corner
of İnegöl.
The ladders are here,
the catapults are here...
the battering ram is here.
So, the war was in İnegöl
for years.
But they didn't know it.
Forgive us, Osman Bey. But when
were we going to hear this?
A secret is a burden, Turgut Bey.
But don't think that I don't
trust you.
-I was capable of carrying it. So I did.
-Thank you.
Now, you know it.
There is more.
Master Davud was working on the
bursting cannon balls of Akça Çoban.
He succeeded.
And we placed them around İnegöl.
The old man was working on it for
a long time. It's the best time to finish.
Now, they don't think that we have
the weapons for a siege.
When they see us, I pity them.
True. True, brother.
It's your task to build the
catapults and start the siege.
Be on your way soon.
As Master Davud said,
''Tomorrow...
we'll be hitting the walls of
İnegöl.''
-Inshallah.
-Inshallah, my bey.
Now is time for conquest.
O' the healer!
Bring down your grace for
your subject, Koses.
Heal him.
For the sake of your
prophet Muhammed.
For the sake of your proper
Jesus.
Heal the wounds of this
wounded subject.
Heal him, my Allah.
Allahu Akbar!
-There is no God but Allah!
-Allahu Akbar!
Osman Bey!
-What happened, Barkın Bey?
-It's not good!
Selvi, my people, they are all
in danger! Help us!
I need your help!
-Who did this?
-That dog Romanus!
He captured Selvi and my people
on their way to the upland.
-In return...
-He wants Nikola in return.
But not only Nikola.
He wants the soldiers you
captured in Bilecik Castle.
If we don't release them, he says
that he'll kill them all.
For Allah's sake,
help us, Osman Bey.
If something happens to my Selvi,
to my people...
Don't worry, Barkın Bey. when did
we ever leave someone behind?
But, there were going to leave
secretly.
Who told the destination?
We have no other chance to
save Nikola, Barkın.
On the way to the upland, we'll capture
Selvi and the tribespeople.
-In return for Nikola--
-No!
I won't let you take Selvi.
Take anyone from the tribe.
-But not Selvi!
-Barkın. Don't worry.
It's just a game. I promise you.
Selvi won't get hurt.
As we talked, Osman Bey.
I didn't tell it to anyone.
They knew it before you left.
We'll find that out later.
But we should think about
what we'll do now.
Barkın! Barkın!
Where is Selvi? What's happening,
Osman Bey? Is it true?
It is, Malhun Hatun. But we'll save Selvi
before they hurt her.
Right, Osman Bey?
We won't leave my sister
to those tyrants, right?
Malhun, be at ease. We'll save Selvi.
When did we ever leave someone
behind, my bey?
True.
We won't Selvi to them.
Look at this smell.
It smells awful.
Disgusting shepherd tent.
Disgusting.
Be happy that I didn't
put you next to the snakes.
You'll go to your castle now.
To my castle?
Are you letting me?
You?
Osman Bey.
What made you change your mind,
Osman Bey?
As I can understand from your silence...
...you couldn't get what you wanted.
I was not intended to stay
in that tent either.
I was going to leave.
Good.
You should know that...
...I will not let you sleep in that
comfy bed in your castle.
You will fear me...
You wonder when I will show up
and kill you.
You won't be able to sleep.
Untie him.
You barbarians!
Hey people!
I want to kill that ignoble...
...the most.
But...
Selvi Hatun...
...and Barkin Bey's people
are captivated.
If the people there gets hurt...
...because of this dog...
...I cannot forgive myself.
Now you tell me!
Can you forgive yourself...
...if they kill our people there...
...because of this infidel?
Tell me!
That ignoble martyred my son.
He burned my heart!
But you are right.
Others shouldn't suffer anymore.
We will wait for our revenge.
Don't worry.
Don't worry at all.
They will not last long.
I swear on the martyrs!
I am going to kill Nikola myself.
But...
...he'll go for the swap now.
Turgut Bey.
I assign you with this important duty.
Bring Selvi Hatun and Barkin Bey's people
safe and sound.
As you say, Osman Bey.
We won't let those dogs play a trick on us.
- Kutan!
- My Bey!
He laughs.
No power could get you out of
this tribe alive...
...if you were more important than
our people.
Come on!
So, my Bey.
What's next?
What will we do?
We won't stop.
If they play a trick on us...
...we'll set up a trick as well.
Let's go!
We will cut all the branches Osman holds.
None will get out of that mine alive!
We will first claim that mine...
...then we will blow that mine up.
Is the Greek fire ready?
Everything is just as you command, sir.
Good.
- Good luck, Hatuns.
- Thank you Ayse Hatun.
Hay Masha Allah!
- Good luck!
- Thank you!
Hatuns!
Inegol preparations are on!
From now on, we'll work for the war.
You'll give a break to weaving rugs.
Ayse Hatun, distribution of the swords
is your responsibility.
You'll produce arrows and shields
with Hatuns.
People from Ahis will come to help you.
Don't worry, Malhun.
Our Alps will have no lackings
with Allah's permit.
Thank Allah.
Alaca, you and hatuns will take care of
Alps' food.
We don't know how long this war last.
So work hard.
As you command, Malhun Hatun.
Kumral Abdal!
How is the healing house?
We allocated the tents near
the healing house...
...to wounded Alps.
Alps are getting the tents ready.
Thank Allah, we have enough herbs...
...and remedies.
Thank Allah.
Aydogdu and hatuns will be responsible
of wounded Alps.
Hatuns, go with Kumral Abdal.
Take what you need.
Have no shortage.
The war has come!
Our Alps and sisters will sweat on
battlefield, we will work here!
Come on!
Kayi needs your service!
Let's do it Hatuns!
Up!
Wait!
Duck!
Faster!
Shoot!
Up!
Wait!
Duck!
Shoot!
Up!
Wait!
Duck!
Shoot!
Up!
Wait!
Duck!
Shoot!
Up!
Wait!
Duck!
What is the situation, Aygul?
Masha Allah(praise be) to them, Bala!
You trained them well.
It is obvious that they learned from you.
The rest of the sisters
are busy helping Hatuns.
The rest of them needs more training.
Good.
Sisters!
My valiant Hatuns!
You proved your skills in
every fight you enganged.
We are proud of you.
Thank you.
Aygül Hatun?
What do you think?
Are the sisters ready for a new war?
Even the most naive sisters are now
ready for the war.
They shoot the target in the first shoot.
Masha Allah.
Masha Allah!
(praise be!)
What is the three rule of...
...sisters?
Take care of your job,
your family and your food!
Hay Masha Allah!
It is time for war!
Our destination is Inegol!
Sisters will not stop until...
...we raise Kayi flags
on the Inegol walls!
May our fight be holy!
Allah is the greatest!
I am not going to kill you now.
We have things to see.
Turgut Bey, ah Turgut Bey.
You should have killed me
when you caught me.
Unfortunately, you failed to do so.
What are you laughing at?
Are you bored of living?
Let me tell you this.
He laughs longest who laughs last
Selvi!
Selvi I'll save you!
Stop Barkin Bey.
We are here to get them
safe and sound.
Turks!
I am seeking opportunity to kill you.
Let it be a clear swap.
Otherwise...
I'll kill the captives first...
...then I'll kill you!
If you bark at Turks like that again,
I'll put a collar on your neck!
Of course the swap will be clear.
There's a idiom that you don't know.
Our words are our honor.
Turgut Bey is right.
We need a clear swap too, Romanos.
Free the captives now.
-Nikola!
-Romanos.
You are still breathing.
I have seen better days.
I want to return to my castle at once!
Because I will end Turks.
Why hurry?
You will get away from us...
...but you'll be close to the
grim reaper.
You are not long for this world.
Samil!
Yes my Bey.
We are always in a fight
since you came.
Thank Allah, my Bey.
Turan, Gencebey, Samil.
You go at this direction.
- As you command, my Bey.
- Eyvallah (thank you).
Boran, Cerkutay, you'll join me.
- Eyvallah (yes) my Bey
You know what to do.
I want no hitch.
We'll reveal the truth.
Let's go
May our fight be blessed!
- Amen
- Amen.
Let's go valiants.
I will send the captives!
Send Nikola and the rest
at the same time.
Come on.
- Kutan
- My Bey.
Let's do it.
Come, brothers.
Come.
Selvi!
Okay, easy.
I was so afraid, Barkin.
I was so afraid.
It's over.
It's all over.
Let's go.
Turgut Bey!
Nikola!
Soldier!
Where is Vasilius?
He is dead.
Turks buried him.
Another reason to burn their tribe.
But I'll wait for Arius to
destroy the mines first.
Turgut Bey.
Alps.
Thank you.
I appreciate this.
- You are fine, right?
- Thank Allah, we are.
Eyvallah (thank you) Turgut Bey.
Eyvallah (sure).
This Nikola got rid of me again!
He did it again!
It's enough!
Not much left, Turgut Bey.
He'll pay for the pain he gave.
Not much left, Nikola.
You won't have anything left
when you lose here, Osman.
We are attacking now.
Kill them all.
Imprison them all in the eternal darkness!
Now!
Let's show those dogs who the boss is.
Brothers, blast the
wind of Caucasian on them!
Let's break their tooth
one by one, brothers.
My sword is out of patience.
The infidel are riding for a fall!
Where are you running, ha?
How could you know we were here?
How did you learn it?
Coward dog.
You are afraid to show your face.
Yet you don't fear my wrath.
Ha?
Let's see.
You came to my tent...
...in guise of Fiqh (fiqh person).
You ate my food.
You were my guest!
How did you catch me?
How?
You!
You are a devil in guise of fiqh!
But I am a wolf in guise of human!
Now you are in my paws.
Came from Aktemur, my Bey.
Arius and Commander Romanus...
...will claim the mines
and blow them up.
They want to prevent us from conquering
Inegol by removing our source of ammunation.
Good.
Let them come.
Let them come and
witness our wrath!
You'll be defeated by our darkness, Osman!
You!
You are a devil in disguise!
You came in my tent.
You ate my food in my table.
You tried to trick us with Quran!
You!
You have betrayed!
You, so it was you behind it all!
Come here!
You tried to lay Sogut at our door!
Come!
You killed Mari, Umur Bey, Ivaz Bey, huh?
Come here.
So you intended to kill Sheik Edebali.
You!
Sheik Edebali.
I made him both live and die.
He lives thanks to me.
Admit it, Osman.
How was my acting?
I acted very well!
I acted looking at you in the eye.
We will always be there
and end you.
We will end you Osman.
You...
...only end yourselves.
So you have been evil for years, huh?
You played many tricks behind us.
But you managed nothing.
I killed many cruels until now.
Now look at me.
These eyes are the last eyes you see!
Last eyes!
Your time is up.
Selvi!
Welcome, sister. Thank to the One who
let you meet us safe and sound.
Thanks to Him, sister.
Welcome Selvi Hatun.
I don't know how to thank you.
And Osman Bey.
How could he release Nikola?
Osman Bey didn't think twice when it came
to the matter of our people's lives.
Thank him.
I was afraid to return empty handed...
...while on my way to the tribe.
But Osman Bey ignored his revenge...
...gave up on Inegol castle
and saved you, Selvi.
I owe Osman Bey a life.
Thank him.
Where is Osman Bey?
I couldn't see him.
Sister.
What is the preparations for?
Preparation for conquest, sister.
Osman Bey went to conquer Inegol.
Hay Masha Allah.
Both Osman Bey and Kayi tribe won't stop!
What we need to do is to help you.
Kizilbeyoglu tribe Hatuns shall join you.
Of course they can.
We need human power.
We'll prepare for the war all together,
Insha Allah.
Insha Allah (if Allah permits) sister.
Insha Allah (if Allah permits)
Did we receive the parts in Cobanpinar?
We received them, my Bey.
Yilanlik
Hacilar.
Yunusici.
Baspinar.
Yirce.
It is now time to...
...combine the catapults' each parts
of which we hided in different places.
Eyvallah my Bey.
Each part you carry contains
the blood and sweat of martyrs!
For the sake of them, we will
destroy...
...the walls of Inegol, Inshallah!
Inshallah my Bey!
Infidels martyred our valiants.
They think they destroyed our ammo.
But they couldn't manage.
Praise be to Allah
The conquest has begun!
The raid has begun!
Praise be to Allah my Bey!
Did we receive the catapults from
Papazik?
We haven't yet, my Bey.
But we will soon, Inshallah.
Come on then, valiants!
We'll start in the name of Allah!
We will set up these catapults and
move them to Inegol walls!
Inshallah my Bey!
- In the name of Allah!
Aya Nikola is back!
Nobody, no single one can captivate me.
They couldn't!
Not only me.
No one can claim my castle either.
Only I, only Aya Nikola can rule it!
I will remove whoever intends!
Always remember!
I am with you.
You are with me.
Moreover, we have a great commander
who recently joined us.
Commander Romanos!
I thirst for blood!
I..
...and Aya Nikola will lead!
And you will follow us, brave soldiers!
- Are you with me?
- We are with you Aya Nikola!
We are with you Commander Romanus!
We are with you Aya Nikola!
I don't want any mistake.
You know what to do...
...when you arrive in the tents.
Don't worry, sir.
Find me if you face any hitch.
Go now.
I wish my mother had been here and seen
Hatuns who work without taking a breath.
She would be very proud.
Right, Aygül?
We don't have anyone to lead
us the way, Bala.
It hurts...
It hurts me the most...
...that I wasn't there when
she took her last breath.
Don't be sad, Aygül.
Thank Allah she had no worries
when she died.
She resigned her soul with peace.
We'll pray for her.
Ah Mother Selcan.
She had been a mother for us too.
It'll be hard to get used to
her absence.
May Allah place her in heaven.
Amen.
Thank you Selvi Hatun.
Ayse!
Stop, don't do it by yourself.
You are fasting.
You'll faint.
I am doing nothing...
...compared to what Alps and sisters
are doing.
It is tiring, but it'll worth it.
Peace be with your hearts, Hatuns!
Do not tire yourself!
Do your job in turns. Have break!
A Kayi Hatun doesn't have a break,
Bala Hatun!
Hay Masha Allah, well said!
We will work on and on
until we conquer Inegol.
Inshallah.
Here are the
Hatuns who were raised by mother Selcan...
Your soul shall rest in peace, mother.
Your children work for your tribe.
Hand it to me, my Alaeddin.
Masha Allah (praise be) to my kids!
My valiants!
Now that we are not allowed to join war,
we want to help.
Masha Allah!
Your time will come.
You'll sweat over your trainings
until your time comes.
Mother Bala is right, my lion.
Your time is soon.
Don't tire yourself more,
beautiful daughter.
Where are you taking the
ammunations, mother? Can we help on the way?
We will take the ammunation to
Inegol Castle with sisters, Alaeddin.
Who is it coming, Baysungur?
Why are the drums being beaten?
Holofire's aunt's soldiers have arrived,
Malhun Hatun.
They have come a long way.
We should host them.
Take them to the guest tents.
I'll them her when I am available.
Come on!
Everybody back to their job!
Go rest, kids.
Osman has nothing in his hand.
I ruined his quarters.
I took his ammunation that he has
saved for years.
And most importantly, mines!
Thanks to Master Arius cleverness!
Osman is nothing without mines!
He is still a great danger.
But I need to give it to Arius.
He always has a plan for future.
This is why we call him master Arius,
Romanus.
I think you need to call him
master Arius as well.
As you can understand from the silence,
he must have already claimed the mines.
How would that be possible?
They were to sneak into near our castle,
build a quarters, and attack with catapults!
Is that so? Hah!
We only stopped their next attack, Nikola!
And I am bored of talking about it.
When Arius comes,
I'll form a great army.
I am not here to stand behind the walls.
I am here to shed blood!
Thank you.
Ey Masha Allah!
Brother!
Tell me, what is the situation?
Those are the last ones.
When we move these too...
all the catapults will be deployed
in front of Inegol Castle, my Bey.
What about their strength?
Are our catapults powerful, brother?
Everything is all ready, right?
They are powerful, Osman Bey.
Don't worry.
We will demolish Inegol walls with
these catapults with Allah's permission.
Inshallah.
We will do it with these Inshallah.
We turned the villagers on their way,
my Bey.
They won't help Inegol.
Another caravan was coming,
we took care of them.
You took care of one, what about the rest?
The roads are in Kayi's control.
Nothing enters, nothing goes out.
We blocked all the aid ways to Inegol.
There is no obstacle left for it to
be Turk's property.
They think we have stopped.
However, we will keep coming at
the cruels.
- Sir.
- Talk.
Sir, it's Osman.
Osman and Turks are coming.
Catapults, battering rams and
many equipments.
If you've burned the catapults...
what are the ones that are coming?
Do you know about the Zumruduanka Bird?
It's name is Turk!
We will resurrect from where we burn
Peace be to Allah.
Burn it Nikola, burn it!
Your prepare your fire in hell!
Zumruduanka.
How did they do it?
How?
Damn it!
How many catapults are there?
Sir, I counted five but
I couldn't count th...
Ah!
I only broke the branches of the tree!
The roots of that tree
reaches up to my castle!
What are you saying Nikola?
Speak clearly.
The trade they did to Inegol, Romanus.
The caravans that carried their goods...
...the caravans that carry their goods...
They only carried their ammunation.
For years.
While we were asking to ourselves
"Where is that quarters of Osman?! Where?!"
They builded the quarters
in front of us!
We couldn't see!
You were the one who should have seen.
You should have seen it.
Our plan is obvious!
We will do what we do the best.
We will fight!
We will fight.
Alps!
Brothers!
Inegol's walls are strong.
But not as strong as our ambition.
Now that they don't accept
surrendering with peace...
...now it's our time.
We'll put a hole in Inegol walls.
When the soldiers start moving...
...our archers will start shooting
their archers on the walls.
But when you try to enter the castle
from those holes...
...they'll pour boiling oil
from the castle.
We will be cautious!
Brothers, may our fight be blessed!
Allah is the greatest!
My Bey!
They are approaching!
They are approaching, yeah.
Which Turkmen Bey could
stop himself from joining war?
They are approaching!
They are approaching.
Byzantine's brave men!
My soldiers!
The day has come.
The enemy who
made a nest in front of our home
is now at the door of our castle!
I, Aya Nikola...
...have felt death at my neck for years.
But I wasn't afraid. I am not afraid.
I will not be afraid!
What are we going to do?
We will cut their breath!
My soldiers! Today you need to entitle...
...your swords and shields!
Death is at the edge of our swords today.
And we will kill Turks...
with these swords in İnegöl.
They will make breaches in our walls.
Don't be afraid and don't step back.
Don't! Because...
we will put Turks' skulls in
those breaches.
My soldiers! Byzantine's brave men...
I, Aya Nikola...
am not afraid!
Don't you be afraid too.
Who wants the shed the blood of
Turks with me?
Us!
- Who?
- Us!
Sir, a riderless horse came here.
Master Arius
Osman.
I promise you.
I will exhibit Osman's
head in every tribe.
I promise.
I'm waiting outside the castle walls.
Osman Bey.
Prepare faster.
Come on.
Wait for me, Osman.
Wait.
Osman Bey, we're here to support you.
Thank you.
Welcome, Turkmen Beys.
For how long do you not
inform us about the raids?
We didn't hear your call, Osman Bey.
Every horse takes you to İnegöl.
The war is here. The conquest is here.
You don't need to be informed. You
know now.
Thank you. Okay, then.
Turkmen Beys...
you accepted to come here
for the conquest.
Thank you all.
Welcome.
Thank you, my Bey.
You're under my command now.
Your Alps will go inside the
breaches with Boran and Konur.
The rest of them will attack from
behind with Turgut Bey.
Those who will come with me...
will break the door of the castle and...
will go inside.
There will be not only us.
Many valiants will also be there.
We haven't stopped since my grandfather Süleyman
Shah and my father Ertuğrul Ghazi.
We won't stop too, and the ones who
will come after us.
May our war be blessed.
- Allah-u Akbar!
My Bey, the doors are opened.
The news are spread.
Come.
Come here.
I will send your food now, you
can rest then.
We're thankful but why is the
tent in a hurry?
Has something dangerous happened?
Nothing to worry about. As
I said, you can rest...
then, Malhun Hatun will talk to you.
You can rest now, we will take action
at the night.
- Nikola.
- Osman Bey.
Give us the castle, peacefully.
Both your castle and your soldiers will
not be harmed.
Don't worry, I will forgive them all.
Will you? Huh?
You're underrating me, Osman Bey.
We have been fighting for years.
Do you think I will give you my castle?
I enslaved many of your acquaintances,
from your family, from your tent...
I also tortured your Alps there.
I won't give you my castle.
I have a memory of it.
That's why I pity you.
You will lose everything that belongs
to you.
Your castle...
Your life...
If you don't surrender, too much
blood will be shed.
You know me well.
I will shed blood.
Your blood will be shed more than ours.
Osman Bey, this is İnegöl.
My land.
I'm not afraid.
My soldiers are not afraid.
I'm warning you one last time.
Give us the castle.
This land's winds are
for Islam flag to fly.
The wind isn't for İnegöl's walls.
There are enough dungeons
for you in my castle and...
there are enough swords to kill you.
Is this your decision?
Yes, it is.
İnegöl is here, come and take it.
If you can.
I did what I had to do.
Okay, then.
We will use our power on İnegöl.
İnegöl belongs to Islam now.
We are the children of those who
aren't afraid to ride anywhere.
We have waited for İnegöl for so much.
Tell the Beys.
Tell the Alps.
Take the catapult, prepare
the battering ram.
Sharpen your swords one last time.
It's time for conquest.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com